https://rivergear.com/contact-us/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Home > Contact Us > Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy – Man of Rubber
Overview
We are committed to your privacy and the protection of your information.
What Personal Information We Collect and Why:
We collect personal information to provide enhanced customer service to you and when you do business with us.  MOR collects and retains customer names, postal and email addresses, billing information, and phone and fax numbers for our own use when you place orders or purchase products from us.
How We Use Your Personal Information:
The collection of customer names, postal and email addresses, billing information, and phone numbers is used for order processing and communication regarding your Man of Rubber order.
Email Newsletters:
When you supply Man of Rubber with your email address, you may receive monthly mailings of the Man of Rubber electronic newsletter.  We use Man of Rubber E-News to notify you of special offers, merchandising tips, and new products. If you would rather not receive this inside information, you may unsubscribe at any time at the bottom of every enewsletter or you may call or email us to manually unsubscribe you.
“Cookies” and Site Usage Tracking:
Rivergear.com uses cookies on our website.  A Cookie is a text file that allows you to retain the contents of your shopping cart while you continue to shop. Cookies also save your personal settings so you don’t have to enter them every time you shop at Rivergear.com. Payment information is not stored in your cookies and the existence of a cookie does not breach your privacy. Cookies save you time by remembering your personalized settings. Cookies are stored as temporary internet files on your computer. In order for somebody to access the information stored in your cookie they would need to hack into your personal computer. The information cannot be accessed through our web server. Cookies are also used by Man of Rubber to collect information on what areas of our web site are most popular, allowing us to better organize our site to suit your needs. We do not use personal information provided for any other purpose.
Cookies and Google Analytics
Man of Rubber uses Google Analytics to help us understand traffic on and manage our website. This is common and used by most websites.  Here is the Google privacy policy so you can see how Google uses cookies to track website activity via aggregating data with no personally identifiable information.  Google Analytics Privacy Policy
Access to Personal Information
If you would like to update, review, or remove your personal information from the Man of Rubber database, please call 1.800-437-9224 , write    Man of Rubber at 204 Estep Road, Reliance TN 37369-6416 or email beth@rivergear.com tell us what you would like us to do.
This Privacy Policy was updated September 28, 2015.
We value your time and interest and won’t clutter your inbox or your mailbox.
We welcome your feedback always – please send email directly to our Head People Person and First Lady ~ The Woman of Rubber: Beth Harper. Or, call us at 1-800-437-9224.
Product CategoriesCOVID 19, Corona Virus Face Mask Coverings (51)
Uncategorized (0)
Gift Card (1)
Paddles & Helmets (17)
Electric Inflators & Pumps (16)
Raft Repair (50)
Raft Valves by Leafield (21)
Sink The Stink & 303 Protectant (4)
Rescue Throw Bags, Biners, and Cam Straps (13)
River Boxes & Bags (29)
SOUL Gear Solar Powered Dry Bags & Accessories (2)
River Camping (8)
Water Shoes and Bandanas (51)
River Jewelry & Accessories (35)
Chums Products (81)
Custom Engraved Wooden Products (23)
Personalized Drink Ware & Tote Bags (13)
Suncare, Personal Care, & Repellents (19)
MoR Logo Fun Stuff (8)
204 Estep Road
Reliance, TN
37369-6416
Phone: 1-800-437-9224
Fax: 423-338-8420
Email: beth@rivergear.com
Subscribe to RiverGear News
Email Address*
First Name
First
CAPTCHA
Copyright © 1985-2019 Man of Rubber River GearServing the needs of the whitewater community since 1983.
MENUMENUHomeShop
Paddles & HelmetsRiver Boxes & BagsThrow Bags, Safety, Biners, & Cam StrapsRiver CampingCOVID-19, Corona Virus Face Mask CoveringsSink The Stink & 303-Gear Maintenence
Raft Inflators & PumpsRaft Valves by LeafieldRaft RepairSolar Dry Bags, Bluetooth & AccessoriesRiver Clothing, Covid-19 Face Coverings and Water ShoesCustomized Engraved Wooden ProductsPersonalized Drinkware & Tote Bags
Suncare, Personal Care, & RepellentsChums ProductsRiver Jewelry & AccessoriesMoR River Gear Fun StuffRiver Gear Gift Cards
Raft Repair SolutionsOutfitter Services
Caring For Your LifejacketsMerchandising MagicResourcesClient & Vendor TestimonialsProduct VideosWholesale PoliciesPre-season Catalog
About
Man of Rubber HistoryPhoto GalleriesWho’s Roscoe?BlogContact
Privacy PolicyRetail Return Policy
My Account
Check Out
Cart
